thecompanystore.com 2009-05-05

# Site Terms of Use - Privacy Policy - Cookies - Security Monitoring - The Company Store

|  |   
---  
|   
---  
|  **  
PLEASE READ CAREFULLY. BY USING THIS SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE TO THESE TERMS OF USE.** If you do not agree with any of the below Terms of Use, do not use this site.   

The Company Store®, The Company Store Group, LLC and Hanover Company Store, LLC, (hereinafter jointly referred to as "The Company Store®", unless specific reference to one of the other entities is required) reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update these Terms of Use, and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations, or updates. 

* Materials You See on this Web Site and Your Use of Them   

* Matter You Submit to The Company Store®    

* Privacy   

* Other Sites Which May Be Linked to this Site   

* Disclaimer   

* Limitation of Liability   

* Termination   

* The Law that Governs this Web Site

**  
THE COMPANY STORE® MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES THAT MATERIALS IN THE SITE ARE APPROPRIATE OR AVAILABLE FOR USE IN LOCATIONS OTHER THAN THE UNITED STATES. THOSE WHO CHOOSE TO ACCESS THIS SITE FROM LOCATIONS OUTSIDE OF THE U.S. DO SO ON THEIR OWN INITIATIVE AND ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR COMPLIANCE WITH LOCAL LAWS, IF AND TO THE EXTENT LOCAL LAWS ARE APPLICABLE.**

All materials on this site, including for example, images, illustrations, and special surveys, sweepstakes, games, contests and promotions, are protected by copyrights which are owned and controlled either by The Company Store Group, LLC, an affiliated entity, or by third parties who have licensed their material to The Company Store® Material from [www.thecompanystore.com](http://www.thecompanystore.com/) may not be copied, downloaded, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any purpose other than your own personal, non-commercial, home use is a violation of U.S. copyright law and applicable international copyright treaties and conventions and/or misuse, misappropriation or infringement of copyright and/or other intellectual property rights held by The Company Store®, The Company Store Group, LLC, or affiliated companies. The use of any such material on any other Web site or networked computer environment is prohibited. 

The trademarks, logos, and service marks (collectively the "Trademarks") which you see on this site are registered and unregistered trademarks of Hanover Company Store, LLC, the participating unaffiliated merchants shown or The Company Store Group, LLC, its affiliates, and others. Nothing in this site grants to you any license or right to use any Trademark displayed on this site without the prior written permission of the owner of the Trademark. Your use or misuse of the Trademarks displayed on this site, or any other content on this site, is strictly prohibited. 

This site is controlled and operated by Hanover Company Store, LLC, from its offices located at: 

The Company Store®   
c/o The Company Store Group, LLC   
1500 Harbor Blvd.  
Weehawken, NJ 07086

with an e-mail address for our **Customer Service Manager of[service@thecompanystore.com](mailto:service@thecompanystore.com).** The phone number is **1-800-323-8000.**  
  
---  
back to top  

The Company Store® welcomes your comments regarding our merchandise and services, including our Web Site. However, any notes, messages, billboard postings, ideas, suggestions, photographs, or other material which you submit to The Company Store® will become property of The Company Store® and The Company Store® shall be entitled to use any kind and nature of material which you submit for any type of use forever including in any media whether now known or hereafter devised. When you submit material to the The Company Store® site, you agree that The Company Store® has the right to publish the material for any type of use as outlined above including for promotional and advertising purposes, without compensation to you of any kind. As a result, you are prohibited from sending us any original creative materials such as stories, product ideas, catalog ideas, or original artwork. Nevertheless, you specifically acknowledge and agree that you are the owner of such material and that there are no adverse demands, claims or suits of any kind concerning such material. You agree to defend and indemnify Hanover Company Store, LLC, its shareholders, officers, directors, employees, agents, distributors, vendors, and affiliates from and against any and all third party claims, demands, liabilities, costs or expenses, including reasonable attorneys' fees, resulting from your breach of any of these terms and conditions.   

back to top  
  
The Company Store®  
500 Company Store Road  
La Crosse, WI 54601-4477  
1-800-323-8000  

Version July 30, 2008 

**Where you go and what you do — What we know without you telling us !**  
Data about your activity while here on this site is automatically provided to The Company Store® when you sign on. For example, we collect the e-mail addresses of visitors and customers who click on The Company Store® marketing links or those who register online at The Company Store® website; we collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, how many visits we get, and information such as where visitors arrived from as far as other sites on the Internet or if they directly typed our website address into their browser. E-mail addresses we collect are only used to transmit promotional e-mail offers to those customers and visitors who voluntarily agree to receive such promotional material from us or to send information about customer transactions. Your e-mail address will never be sold or shared for marketing purposes. 

If you would prefer not to receive such e-mails, please **click here**. 

**Cookies — How we know what we know without you telling us !**  
When you come to The Company Store® or when you register with The Company Store® we create your personal profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your computer's hard drive in the form of a "cookie," which is a very small bit of code. A "cookie" is very small text file placed on your hard drive by a Web Page server. It serves as your personal identification card, and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. The use of cookies is an industry standard; you will find them at most major Web sites. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. 

Cookies enable us to know more about your use of the site, and allow you to utilize some of our website's functionality, and correspond with us about your personal profile without having to fill out registration forms with information you've already provided. We use cookies to record session information, such as items that you added to your shopping cart and to conduct marketing tests on our Web pages. By showing how and when you use the site, cookies help us see which areas and products are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our visitors' needs. The purpose of a "cookie" is to tell the server that you returned to that Web page. Of course, if you never register or leave personal information with The Company Store® then the server only knows that someone with your cookie has returned to the Web site. You are in charge of deciding whether we know anything about you. But the more you tell us about yourself, the more we can help you find information or products you want. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the The Company Store® website and its functionality and links will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, entering giveaways, or creating your personal profile. You can order your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered. Then you can decide whether to accept one or not. If you want to control which cookies your computer accepts, just follow the instructions for your particular Internet browser system located at <http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.mspx>. 

**Your E-mail address — Do We Know It ?**  
Your E-mail address and other personally identifying data about you is known to The Company Store® only when you voluntarily submit it to The Company Store® or if you click on one of our promotional e-mail marketing links. We may collect your e-mail address if you post a message to us, if you communicate with us via e-mail, if you ask us to communicate with you by e-mail such as for a confirmation of your order or shipment advice, or if you volunteer it for any reason, such as survey information and/or site registration, or sign-up for a Newsletter, and if you started but did not complete an order. 

**Your E-mail address — What Do We Do With It ?**  
If you begin to place an order from this website, and if you have at any time given us your e-mail address, we may use your e-mail address to communicate with you about the status of your order. We may also send you e-mails regarding special sales, exclusive offers, and other valuable promotions that we think will interest you if you have voluntarily agreed to receive such promotional material. 

If you enter one of our giveaways, Tel.e.Friend® about one of our products, or sign up for one of our Newsletters, and give us your e-mail address, we may use your e-mail address not only for the purpose it was submitted, but also to send you e-mails regarding our own special sales, exclusive offers, and other valuable promotions that we think may interest you if you have voluntarily agreed to receive such promotional material. 

Like many other online merchants, we participate in cooperative database services which assist us in the matching of offline and online purchasing behavior, and marketing analysis, so that participants can better analyze and understand the differences and tendencies of print catalog purchasers and website visitors, and so that we can maximize the benefit of postal mail and e-mail we send to you. This sharing of information allows us and other interested parties to make future marketing efforts more efficient. These cooperative database services and their participants, however, are not authorized by The Company Store® to use your e-mail address to send you e-mail. 

If you would prefer not to receive emails from us regarding special sales and exclusive offers, **click here**.

If you would prefer not to receive emails regarding the status of your order, **click here**.

**Personal Information Other Than Your E-mail Address.**  
Your California Privacy Rights The Company Store® has a policy of not disclosing the personal information of our customers to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes if our customers have exercised their option to prevent that information from being disclosed to third parties for such purposes. The following paragraphs explain what we do with your personal information and how you can prevent it, or simply **click here to change your privacy preferences**. 

We use your shipping and payment address, and the address you give to us when you "register" your profile with us, to send you our print catalog and catalogs of our participating third-party merchants and affiliated companies which we feel will be of interest to you, all by postal mail. 

If you have given us your telephone number, when registering your profile with us or when ordering merchandise from us, we may use your telephone number to reach out to you to follow up on your order of merchandise, including follow-up marketing. We do not share your telephone number with any outside parties for any purpose whatsoever. 

We indefinitely maintain all of the information you give to us, to help us serve you better and to understand our customers and their purchasing patterns over time. Any payment information that is maintained by us is masked to keep it protected in the unlikely event of unauthorized breaches of security. 

In addition, we may also share your name, address, e-mail address and purchase information directly with select merchants who are marketing affiliates of ours or other third parties. We use this information to match against our own offline catalog information (available from our records and other sources, such as demographic information and past purchase history) and we allow our marketing affiliates to use this information to match against their own offline information (available from their records and other sources, such as demographic information and past purchase history). This sharing of information allows us and other interested parties to make future marketing efforts more efficient. It may be used by our select marketing affiliates to send you offers of interest, by regular postal mail. If at any time we are required to share your full credit card information with marketing affiliates so they can bill you for a product or service, you will be made aware at the time of offer that the product or service is being provided directly by that vendor and we will clearly ask for your consent to make that transfer of your credit card information through secure transmission. 

Like many other online merchants, we participate in cooperative database services which assist us in the matching of offline and online purchasing behavior so that participants can better analyze and understand the differences and tendencies of print catalog purchasers and website visitors and we can maximize the benefit of postal mail and e-mail we send to you if you have signed up with us to receive postal mail or e-mail. It may be used by other cooperative database participants to send you offers of interest, by postal mail. 

If you prefer that we do not include you in lists of information we share with others, **click here**. 

**Opt-Out of Future Catalogs.**  
If you have requested a catalog from us, or have purchased from us at any time, we will send you one of our catalogs. If for any reason you no longer wish to receive catalogs from The Company Store® or Company Kids®, please contact Customer Service at 1(800)323-8000. 

**Correction of Your Personal Profile.**  
You can always edit or correct any personal information you give The Company Store® by writing to us at: [custserv@thecompanystore.com](mailto:custserv@thecompanystore.com). 

**Shopping Analysis Provided by Third Party.**  
The Company Store® uses a number of third party data gathering and analysis services, which aggregate information into broad categories to help us provide you better products, services, and improved websites. We refer to them here as our "Data Compilers". Our Data Compilers are contractually bound to keep our visitors’ and customers’ data absolutely secure and confidential, and only to analyze the information they have access to by the software we license from them and return it back to The Company Store®. They have no rights to use this information for any purpose, match it against any other information in their possession, nor transfer or disclose this information to anyone other than to The Company Store®. 

**Customer Privacy During Tracking By Our Data Compilers.**  
Our Data Compilers have adopted privacy guidelines set by the Federal Trade Commission. The Company Store® relies on our Data Compilers and encourages you to learn more about our each of their Privacy Standards and any available opt-out choices by [clicking here](http://www.coremetrics.com/privacy.html) [(Coremetrics)](http://www.coremetrics.com/privacy.html), [clicking here](http://www.quigo.com/privacy.htm) [(Quigo)](http://www.quigo.com/privacy.htm), and [clicking here](http://www.atlassolutions.com/privacy/) [(Atlas Solutions)](http://www.atlassolutions.com/privacy/). 

**Access by The Operator of Our Affiliates Program**  
As a visitor to the The Company Store® site, you may have arrived here through a link on one of our affiliate sites. Our affiliates operate websites which they use to conduct a business or generate revenues, and The Company Store® compensates its affiliates based upon any purchases made by an affiliate-linked visitor to The Company Store® site. The operator of our affiliates program, Commission Junction, in providing its services to us, does not deal directly with our customers. A visitor who clicks on a The Company Store® link located on an affiliate's website is redirected, invisibly, through the website of Commission Junction, where its technology automatically records the IP "address" of the browser used by the visitor, but that address does not permit identification of the individual using the browser. In addition, during such redirection, Commission Junction may place a "cookie" on the hard drive of the visitor's computer through his or her Web browser (See description of cookies above). Commission Junction does not have access to data that identifies or permits the identification of any of The Company Store® customers or visitors. The operator of our affiliates program encourages you to learn more about its privacy standards by clicking here.  
<http://www.cj.com/privacy.jsp>

**Access By the Operator of Our Security Monitor**  
As a visitor to The Company Store® site, the operator of our security monitor, ScanAlert will have access to your activity here. This web site is tested and certified daily to pass the FBI/SANS Internet Security Test. ScanAlert's security auditing technology allows the HACKER SAFE logo to appear only when a web site's current security status meets the highest published government standards. The access which we allow to ScanAlert for its HACKER SAFE service help protect you from identity theft and credit card fraud. According to ScanAlert, "HACKER SAFE does not mean hacker proof. HACKER SAFE certification cannot and does not protect any of your data that may be shared with other servers that are not certified HACKER SAFE, such as credit card processing networks or offline data storage, nor does it protect you from other ways your data may be illegally obtained such as non-hacker "insider" access to it. For more information about the privacy policies of ScanAlert and HACKER SAFE, go to <http://www.mcafee.com/us/about/privacy.html>. 

**Access by Third Party Advertising Companies**  
From time to time, we may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. In the course of serving advertisements to this and other sites, these companies usually collect information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our ads. Any information that these third parties collect is completely anonymous, is in a non-personal aggregate format, and is shared for purposes of analysis and improvement of our site. For instance, they may keep track of how many of our ads you had seen before visiting our site. This is primarily accomplished through technology, including cookies and action tags (commonly referred to as Web Beacons or GIF tags), which we will place on various pages within our Web site. These third party advertising companies may, in turn, use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide ads about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about the practices of our third party advertising contractors, if any, and to know how to contact them to advise them of your choices about not having your information used further, please [**click here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**Access By Other Corporate Entities**  
We share much of our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with our parent company Hanover Direct, Inc., and its subsidiaries and affiliated catalog and e-commerce companies and other third parties. To the extent that you are not already a customer of such entity, they will do nothing with the information and will treat it at least as protectively as we treat the information we have about you. If you are already a customer of such entity, they may use this information to serve your needs better with respect to their merchandising, promotion, and marketing. We reserve the right to sell our customer database in the event The Company Store® is acquired, dissolved, declared insolvent, files for bankruptcy or undergoes some other corporate change for which The Company Store® is materially affected. If you are a customer of another Hanover Direct catalog company and prefer that we do not include you in lists of information we share with one of our affiliated marketing companies which they may use for promotion or marketing, please **click here**. 

It is possible that The Company Store® Hanover Direct, or its affiliated companies, or any combination, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that The Company Store® would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide The Company Store® shopping experience. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent it occurs) as provided in the paragraph below entitled "Notice"", and we will require that the new combined entity follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information. 

**Problems**  
If at any time you have a question or dispute concerning your visit here, your order transaction, or our compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us at [custserv@thecompanystore.com](mailto:custserv@thecompanystore.com). Please provide your first and last name, order number, if any, and, if you have a question about our merchandise, item number(s), and we will get back to you promptly. If we are unable to resolve your complaint to your satisfaction, you may elect to proceed to submit your complaint to an independent arbitrator to obtain an impartial assessment of your case, in writing. Any such arbitration will be deemed "conditionally binding", meaning that the decision of the arbitrator will be binding upon The Company Store® if you elect to accept the decision, and it will be binding upon you as well. If your dispute concerns our compliance with this privacy policy, and if we are unable to resolve your complaint to your satisfaction, you may elect to proceed with BBB OnLine"s Privacy Policy Review Service by completing the [BBBOnline complaint form](http://www.bbbonline.org/about/privacy.asp). 

**To Residents of a European Union Member Country (EU Residents) - Re: The DMA Safe Harbor Program**  
If you are an EU Resident, your personal data in the possession or control of The Company Store® is subject to the United States-European Union Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, FAQ"s and other relevant EU documents (the "Safe Harbor"). Safe Harbor Privacy Principles are made available by the U.S. Department of Commerce on their website at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/SHPRINCIPLESFINAL.htm>. FAQs and other relevant Safe Harbor documents are made available by the U.S. Department of Commerce on their website at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

If you are an EU Resident, in the event you are not satisfied with the resolution by The Company Store® of any questions or complaints you may have regarding your personal data in our possession, then you may submit your questions and complaints to the Direct Marketing Association ("DMA") Safe Harbor Enforcement Program as follows: e-mail: [safeharbor@the-dma.org](mailto:safeharbor@the-dma.org); mail: Safe Harbor Line, Direct Marketing Association, 1615 L Street, NW, Suite 1100, Washington, DC 20036, USA, Telecopier: 202-955-0085; Telephone: 202-861-2445. 

**Security.**  
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our customers and visitors is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, The Company Store® cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When your credit card information is transmitted to The Company Store® we use industry standard, 3.0 SSL (secure socket layer) encryption to ensure the security of your information. 

**Important update about SSL Technology**  
Web browsers (such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari) support SSL technology to encrypt, or encode, your personal information before it is sent over the Internet.   SSL versions 1.0 and 2.0 found in older browsers have known security weaknesses which could compromise your data. To ensure you're getting the best protection available, The Company Store.com only allows secure transactions with browsers using SSL version 3.0 or higher. We recommend upgrading to the latest version of your browser software and downloading security updates as they become available.

The following browsers do support SSL version 3.0, however, if you do not upgrade to the newest versions you may need to change your browser settings to utilize it:

*       Internet Explorer 5.5 or higher (PC)  
*       Internet Explorer 5.0 or higher (Mac)  
*       Netscape 2.0 (Domestic) or higher (PC/Mac)  
*       Firefox 0.8 or higher (PC/Mac/Linux)  
*       Mozilla 1.7 or higher (PC/Mac/Linux)  
*       Camino 0.8 or higher (Mac)  
*       Safari 1.0 or higher (Mac)  
*       Opera 1.7 or higher (PC/Mac)  
*       Omniweb 3.0 or higher (Mac)  
*       Konqueror 2.0 or higher (Linux)

We also have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at The Company Store **®** Nothwithstanding the foregoing, due to the open nature of the internet, We do not guarantee the absence of theft, hacker activity, electronic or non-electronic tampering, or computer crime, and we hereby disclaim responsibility and liability for stolen information. 

**Disclaimer.**  
The Privacy Policy expressed herein and these statements constitute the present policy of The Company Store® as to which it will take reasonable measures to implement. Similarly this Privacy Policy is not intended to be "advertising" or "advertising claims." Rather it is intended to set forth our policy, including our practices and intentions about how we conduct our business. 

**Notice**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. All changes to this policy which we deem material and which affect your personal identifiable information, are effective only after we provide you with at least thirty (30) days' notice of the changes by posting the changes here in Terms & Conditions for Use of Site and sending an e-mail to users who have provided us their e-mail address for this purpose. We provide you with thirty (30) days' notice to give you the opportunity to notify us if you do not agree to the changes we highlight to you in our e-mail notice. Our e-mails will normally remind you that you have the opportunity to inform us of your preferences, and will alert you how to inform us of your preferences by such e-mails and through this Privacy Policy. If we make any changes which have no effect upon the collection of your personal information (i.e., revisions to our access and access of third parties to your activities here on an anonymous basis only), then you will not receive an e-mail notification of the change. Such changes will become effective five (5) days after we post the revision to our Privacy Policy on this site.   
  
back to top  

The Company Store® may include some links to other Internet sites maintained by The Company Store Group, LLC or third parties for your convenience only ("Linked Sites"). Neither The Company Store® The Company Store Group, LLC, its subsidiary companies, shareholders, nor their affiliates operate or control in any respect any information, products or services on Linked Sites which are not owned or controlled by an affiliate of The Company Store Group, LLC You access them at your own risk and by accessing them you leave the The Company Store® site. The Company Store® and The Company Store Group, LLC, whether or not we have a relationship with Linked Sites, are not responsible for the content on the Linked Sites and disclaims all liability for any injury you experience while you are in such Linked Site.   
  
back to top  

THE MATERIALS IN THIS SITE AND ANY THIRD-PARTY SITES ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. HANOVER COMPANY STORE, LLC AND THE COMPANY STORE GROUP, LLC. DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. HANOVER COMPANY STORE, LLC AND THE COMPANY STORE GROUP, LLC. DO NOT WARRANT THAT THE MATERIALS WILL BE ACCURATE, RELIABLE OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS SITE, INCLUDING BULLETIN BOARDS, OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE, ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS, OR THAT THIS SITE OR THE TECHNOLOGY THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE, ARE IMMUNE TO HACKER ACTIVITY, ELECTRONIC OR NON-ELECTRONIC TAMPERING, COMPUTER CRIME, OR THEFT. HANOVER COMPANY STORE, LLC AND THE COMPANY STORE GROUP, LLC. DO NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE MATERIALS IN THIS SITE OR IN LINKED SITES IN TERMS OF THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE. 

The material that you read in the The Company Store® site is provided solely for entertainment, promotional, and commercial purposes. 

Typographical Errors: Although all information on this website and in our print catalogs has been carefully checked for accuracy, typographical errors and omissions occur and are therefore subject to correction. We regret any inconvenience. 

back to top  

Neither The Company Store® The Company Store Group, LLC nor its affiliated or related entities or its vendors or content providers are responsible or liable to any person or entity whatsoever for any direct or indirect loss, damage (whether actual, consequential, punitive, special or otherwise), injury, claim, liability or other cause of any kind or character whatsoever based upon or resulting from (1) any The Company Store® information or opinions provided on the The Company Store® site or from the use of, or the inability to use, The Company Store® materials on the site, or (2) any electronic or non-electronic tampering with the site, hacker activity, computer crime, or theft of personal information. You specifically agree that Hanover Company Store, LLC and The Company Store Group, LLC are not liable for any defamatory, offensive or illegal conduct of any user, or for any illegal tampering with the site, hacker activity, computer crime, or theft of your personal information. If you are dissatisfied with the The Company Store® site or any materials on the site, or with any of the The Company Store® Terms of Use, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the The Company Store® site. 

back to top  

These Terms of Use constitute an agreement which is effective until terminated by The Company Store® at any time, without notice. The Company Store® may terminate your right to use this site immediately without notice to you if, in The Company Store's sole and absolute discretion, you fail to comply with any of these Terms of Use. In the event of termination, you are no longer authorized to access the The Company Store® site, and the restrictions imposed upon you with respect to material copied or downloaded, and the disclaimers and limitations of liabilities set forth in these Terms of Use, shall survive the termination of this agreement. These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between you and The Company Store® relating to the subject matter addressed herein. 

back to top  

This agreement is governed by and shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New Jersey, the principal place of business of The Company Store® without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law. You agree to bring any claims against Hanover Company Store, LLC, exclusively in the state or federal courts of New Jersey. If any provision of these Terms of Use shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. 

**MISUSE**  
You specifically agree not to interfere with the operation of The Company Store® web sites(s) or otherwise use such web site(s) for an illegal or improper purpose. 

**CONSENT**  
You acknowledge and agree that your use of The Company Store® web site(s) constitutes your consent to these Legal Terms and Conditions of Use and the privacy policies of The Company Store®. 

back to top
